To summarize, type checking proves facts with a form, E has type
综上所述，类型检查用表格证明事实，E有类型
T And notice that this proof is on the structure of the abstract syntax tree.
t，注意这个证明是关于抽象语法树的结构的。
So, for the expression one+2, we prove something about one+2, but by first proving
所以，对于表达式1+2，我们证明了关于1+2的一些东西，但是首先证明
something about each of the sub-expressions. So we prove that the sub-expressions
关于每个子表达式的一些信息。所以我们证明了子表达式
had type int. And then we managed to prove that the whole thing had
具有类型int。然后我们设法证明了整件事
type int. And so the proof has the same shape as the abstract syntax tree. You can
键入int。因此证明具有与抽象语法树相同的形状。你可以的
look at this proof as a tree. Now the root of the tree in the case of the proof is at
把这个证明看作是一棵树。现在，在证明的情况下，树的根是在
the bottom, we usually draw the abstract syntax tree with the root at the top, so this
在底部，我们通常绘制抽象语法树，根在顶部，所以这个
tree looks like this, whereas we often draw the abstract syntax tree in the
树看起来像这样，而我们通常在
other way around. But, the important thing here is that the proof has the shape of the
反过来说。但是，这里重要的是证明的形状是
abstract syntax tree and there's one type rule that's used for each abstract syntax
抽象语法树，每个抽象语法都有一个类型规则
tree node. So there's a very direct correspondence between the structure of the
树节点。所以在这些结构之间有一个非常直接的对应关系
proof and the shape of the abstract syntax tree. And in general the type rule
证明和抽象语法树的形状。一般情况下，类型规则
used for a particular node of the abstract syntax string, the hypothesis, are going to
用于抽象语法字符串的特定节点，假设将
be the proofs of the type of E's sub-expressions. So, whatever sub-expressions
是E的子式类型的证明。所以，不管是什么子表达式
make up E we're going to need types for them first. And the conclusion
补上E，我们首先需要他们的类型。而结论是
at, at that particular node will be the type of the entire expression
在，在该特定节点处将是整个表达式的类型
E. And this way you can that types are computed in a bottom up pass over the abstract
即，通过这种方式，您可以在抽象上以自下而上的方式计算类型
syntax string. That is I assign first types to the leads. Like here I know
语法字符串。也就是说，我将第一种类型分配给引线。就像这里，我知道
that one has type int and two has type int and then. The types flow towards the root.
一个有int类型，两个有int类型，然后。类型流向根。
I'm able to compute then the next level abstract of syntax tree and so on And then
我可以计算语法树的下一级抽象，依此类推
once I computed the types of all the sub expression of a knob. Then I can compute the
一旦我计算了旋钮的所有子表达式的类型。然后我就可以计算
type at that knob.
按那个旋钮打字。